(Leonard:)I don't want to listen
to music, Sheldon.
(Sheldon-bot:)Very well.
(Sheldon-bot:)I don't understand
why you're not enjoying this.
(Sheldon-bot:)Together, in this car,
with my enhanced capabilities,
we're like Knight Rider.
Except in Knight Rider, the car
isn't a yammering sphincter.
(Sheldon-bot:)You mock the sphincter,
(Sheldon-bot:)but the sphincter
is a class of muscle
(Sheldon-bot:)without which human beings
couldn't survive.
(Sheldon-bot:)There are over 50
different sphincters
(Sheldon-bot:)in the human body.
(Sheldon-bot:)How many can you name?
I was wrong-- this is exactly
like Knight Rider.
(Sheldon-bot:)Perhaps you'd be interested
in a different game.
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon-bot:)This is a photograph of the 1911
(Sheldon-bot:)Solvay Conference on the theory
of radiation and quanta.